import React from "react";
import "./style.css";

let QuestionsArr=[
  {
    question:"How many ballon D'ors ronaldo has won?",
    options:["5","7","4","6"],
    Answer:"5"
  },
  {
    question:"Real madrid 3 peat period _______",
    options:["2017-2019","2016-2018","2014-2017","2019-2022"],
    Answer:"2016-2018"
  },
  {
    question:"who won ballon D'or in 2018?",
    options:["Ronaldo","Messi","Benzema","Modric"],
    Answer:"Modric"
  },
  {
    question:"2018 worldcup host was ______",
    options:["Spain","Qatar","Russia","Brazil"],
    Answer:"Russia"
  },
  {
    question:"which of the following player not played for real madrid?",
    options:["Kubo","Robben","Kovacic","Falcao"],
    Answer:"Falcao"
  },


  {
    question:"2010 World Cup Runner was _____ National Team",
    options:["Nederland","England","Spain","SouthAfrica"],
    Answer:"Nederland"
  },
  {
    question:"2016-2017 UCL Runner",
    options:["Atletico de Madrid","Barcelona","Juventus","Bayern"],
    Answer:"Juventus"
  },
  {
    question:"UEFA - is the governing body of ______",
    options:["South America","Asia","Africa","Europe"],
    Answer:"Europe"
  },
  {
    question:"_______ is not a Serie A team",
    options:["Napoli","Torino","Leeds Utd","Roma"],
    Answer:"Leeds Utd"
  },
  {
    question:"Select the club which Ronaldo didn't played for",
    options:["Al nasr","PSG","Juventus","Sporting"],
    Answer:"PSG"
  },
  {
    question:"Who have won the premier league most?",
    options:["Man Utd","Man City","Chelsea","Liverpool"],
    Answer:"Man Utd"
  },
  {
    question:"Who have won the La Liga most?",
    options:["Barcelona","Atletico de Madrid","Sevilla","Real Madrid"],
    Answer:"Real Madrid"
  },
  {
    question:"ballon D'or Winner in 2022?",
    options:["Benzema","Modric","Salah","Vinicius Jr"],
    Answer:"Benzema"
  },
  {
    question:"International Top Goal Scorer is?",
    options:["Neymar","Ronaldo","Chettri","Messi"],
    Answer:"Ronaldo"
  },
  {
    question:"Which of the following player not played for Chelsea?",
    options:["A Morata","T Abraham","T Werner","None of the above"],
    Answer:"None of the above"
  },
  {
    question:"Brazil Eliminated from _______ in 2014 WC",
    options:["Semi-finals","Quater-finals","RO16","Group-stage"],
    Answer:"Semi-finals"
  },
  {
    question:"UCL all time top goalscorer?",
    options:["Aguero","Ronaldo","Messi","Lewandowski"],
    Answer:"Ronaldo"
  },
  {
    question:"Who of the below is not a Midfielder?",
    options:["Enzo fernandez","thiago alcantara","Kovacic","Araujo"],
    Answer:"Araujo"
  },
  {
    question:"Zlatan Ibrahimovic not played for ________",
    options:["LA Galaxy","Chelsea","Ajax","Man Utd"],
    Answer:"Chelsea"
  },
  {
    question:"Portugal Euro winning Year?",
    options:["2012","2020","2016","Never Won"],
    Answer:"2016"
  },  
]

export default QuestionsArr;
